A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Project Files, 1924-1999; 2
  - Programs, 1924-1998; 1
    - Programs, 1955-1998; D
      - Program and Project Files - Programs - Programs - Grant Classification Scheme (NTEE-National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities), 1985-1994; 5
        - Authority List, 1990 (Reel 118, Frame 508)
        - James Calloway - Trinity Grants Program, 1989-1990 (Reel 118, Frame 533)
        - Classification - Mini-Database, 1989-1990 (Reel 118, Frame 647)
        - Coding, 1988-1989 (Reel 118, Frame 700)
        - Common Codes, 1991 (Reel 118, Frame 872)
        - COMSEARCH, 1990 (Reel 118, Frame 877)
        - Council Meeting, 1989-1990 (Reel 118, Frame 957)
        - Database, 1985 (Reel 118, Frame 1021)
        - Database - Regenerating, 1985-1986 (Reel 118, Frame 1074)
        - Dear Colleague Letter and Order Form, 1991 (Reel 118, Frame 1184)
        - DIALOG, 1989-1990 (Reel 118, Frame 1188)
        - Donors Forum of Chicago, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 1)
        - FD II - Grants Processing Issues, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 3)
        - Field Tags, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 11)
        - Foreign Countries, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 44)
        - Foundation Center - New FC-400 Form, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 59)
        - The Foundation Center's Grants Classification System, undated (Reel 119, Frame 92)
        - Foundation News Articles, 1990-1991 (Reel 119, Frame 203)
        - Fund-Raising, 1989-1991 (Reel 119, Frame 289)
        - Global Coding - Modifiers TR, GP, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 375)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, Chicago, June 14, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 397)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, Cooperating Collection Meeting, Training Manual, Working Draft, July 1988 (Reel 119, Frame 427)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, Minneapolis, June 15, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 436)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, New York, September 27, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 464)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, New York, October 9, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 555)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, New York, November 29, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 560)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops - Additional Meetings, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 577)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, New York, February 7, 1991 (Reel 119, Frame 602)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, San Francisco, February 25, 1991 (Reel 119, Frame 615)
        - Grants Classification System Workshops, Washington, D. C., January 14, 1991 (Reel 119, Frame 651)
        - Grants Index, 1988-1994 (Reel 119, Frame 668)
        - Grants Index Quarterly, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 730)
        - Guide to the Classification System - Drafts, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 779)
        - ISD Output Request Form, 1989-1990 (Reel 119, Frame 911)
        - Key Work Project, 1985-1988 (Reel 119, Frame 920)
        - Key Work Taxonomy, 1980-1983 (Reel 119, Frame 1185)
        - Location Records Added, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 1246)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Reel 119, Frame 1253)
          See also floppy disks in Box 1, Folder 3.
        - MPLS, 1990 (Reel 120, Frame 1)
        - National Taxonomy Committee, 1990-1991 (Reel 120, Frame 159)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities, 1988-1990 (Reel 120, Frame 345)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities, 1990 (Reel 120, Frame 557)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities - Development, 1988 (Reel 120, Frame 624)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities - Reports, 1987-1990 (Reel 120, Frame 680)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities - Translate Tables, 1990-1991 (Reel 120, Frame 810)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities - Twenty Six Major Fields, 1990-1991 (Reel 120, Frame 861)
        - National Taxonomy of Exempt Entities/Foundation Center - Comparison Study, 1988 (Reel 120, Frame 908)
        - New York Taxonomy Workshop, 1990 (Reel 120, Frame 987)
        - Regional Associations of Grantmakers, 1990-1991 (Reel 120, Frame 1122)
        - Reprints, 1991 (Reel 120, Frame 1133)
        - Source Book Profiles Issues, 1989-1990 (Reel 120, Frame 1149)
        - Status Report, 1990 (Reel 120, Frame 1201)
        - Style Manual and Indexing Notes, 1982-1984 (Reel 121, Frame 1)
        - Taxonomy Contacts Database, 1990-1991 (Reel 121, Frame 167)
        - Taxonomy - Draft Versions - Fall, 1990 (Reel 121, Frame 180)
        - Taxonomy - Test, undated (Reel 121, Frame 580)
        - Telecommunications Cooperative Network, 1990 (Reel 121, Frame 598)
        - Thesaurus Project, 1977 (Reel 121, Frame 613)
        - Washington, D. C. Taxonomy Workshop, 1990-1991 (Reel 121, Frame 670)
      - Program and Project Files - Programs - Programs - Major Gift Campaign, 1979-1991; 6
        This series describes a large fund-raising campaign that was to raise $7.5 million for a 5 year program to build the Foundation Center's capacities to meet the growing information needs in the field of private philanthropy, primarily in the area of technology.
        - Audit Report, 1979-1986 (Reel 121, Frame 750)
        - Budget and Finance, 1986-1989 (Reel 121, Frame 871)
        - Brochure - Roger Williams, 1987-1988 (Reel 121, Frame 905)
        - Campaign Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Reel 121, Frame 987)
        - Campaign Organizing Committee - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Reel 121, Frame 1082)
        - Campaign Organizing Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1986-1988 (Reel 121, Frame 1131)
        - Campaign Plans - Phase I and II, 1987-1992 (Reel 121, Frame 1264)
        - Eleanor Cicerchi - Campaign Director, 1986 (Reel 121, Frame 1279)
        - Eleanor Cicerchi - Chronological Files, 1985-1987 (Reel 122, Frame 1)
        - Eleanor Cicerchi - Chronological Files, 1987-1988 (Reel 122, Frame 686)
        - Eleanor Cicerchi - Correspondence and Memorandum, 1986-1988 (Reel 122, Frame 1170)
        - Expenditures and Allocations, 1987-1991 (Reel 123, Frame 1)
        - Financial Reports, 1987-1988 (Reel 123, Frame 79)
        - Fund-Raising Advisory Committee, 1985-1989 (Reel 123, Frame 94)
        - Fund-Raising Advisory Committee - Sara L. Engelhardt, 1985-1987 (Reel 123, Frame 303)
        - Fund-Raising Progress Report, 1986 (Reel 123, Frame 342)
        - Generic Proposals, 1987-1988 (Reel 123, Frame 359)
        - Gift Range Tables, undated (Reel 123, Frame 383)
        - Highlights and Significant Accomplishments, 1988-1991 (Reel 123, Frame 391)
        - Income, 1987-1992 (Reel 123, Frame 397)
        - The Robert Woods Johnson Foundation, 1988 (Reel 123, Frame 416)
        - Key Statements, undated (Reel 123, Frame 458)
        - The Kresge Foundation, 1988-1989 (Reel 123, Frame 494)
        - Major Gift Campaign Dinner, November 21, 1988 (Reel 123, Frame 543)
        - Russ Mawby - Campaign Chair, 1986-1988 (Reel 123, Frame 601)
        - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Reel 123, Frame 763)
        - Needs, 1986-1988 (Reel 123, Frame 779)
        - Opinion of Counsel, 1987 (Reel 123, Frame 889)
        - Pew Memorial Trust, 1988-1989 (Reel 123, Frame 895)
        - Phase II - Board Meeting, May 15, 1989 (Reel 123, Frame 907)
        - Phase II - Correspondence, 1988-192 (Reel 123, Frame 937)
        - Phase II - Declinations, 1990-1992 (Reel 123, Frame 1031)
        - Phase II - Prospects Lists, 1988-1990 (Reel 123, Frame 1039)
        - Phase II - Strategy, 1988-1989 (Reel 123, Frame 1115)
        - Planning Task Force, 1986-1988 (Reel 123, Frame 1193)
        - Walter Plotch, 1983-1990 (Reel 124, Frame 1)
        - Pre and Early Campaign, 1982-1986 (Reel 124, Frame 117)
        - Presentation, undated (Reel 124, Frame 289)
        - Proposal List and Prospectus Reports, 1986-1987 (Reel 124, Frame 300)
        - Publication Project Budget, 1988 (Reel 124, Frame 375)
        - Regional Cultivation and Reports, 1987-1988 (Reel 124, Frame 380)
        - Reports to Major Gift Donors, 1986-1992 (Reel 124, Frame 427)
        - Restrictions on Grants - Legal Advice, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 577)
        - Services to New York City and Washington, D. C. Reports, 1988-1989 (Reel 124, Frame 584)
        - Solicitation Status Reports, 1987-1992 (Reel 124, Frame 598)
        - Strategic Planning, 1987-1992 (Reel 124, Frame 674)
        - Timeline and Schedules, 1986-1988 (Reel 124, Frame 814)
        - Weekly Situation Reports, 1986-1988 (Reel 124, Frame 873)
      - Program and Project Files - Programs - Programs - Public Services Seminars, 1966-1992; 7
        This series contains materials on the seminars that The Foundation Center gave in various cities to help grant seekers of non-profit organizations who wanted to enhance their understanding of the grant-seeking process and other aspects of outside funding.
        - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - 'A Grantmakers Introduction to the Foundation Center', undated; Audio-Cassette (Box 1, Folder 1)
          See also Reel 125, Frames 1105, 1154, 1171.
        - Congressional Seminars, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          Foundation Center, Capital Hill, contact sheet, March 13, 1992 Photographer: Anna Ng
          See also Reel 125, Frame 0130.
        - AIDS Funding Sessions, March 1 and 7, 1987 (Reel 124, Frame 1139)
        - Bibliographies on Philanthropic Foundations, 1966-1970 (Reel 124, Frame 1192)
        - Centerline News - Transcripts, 1977-1979 (Reel 125, Frame 1)
        - Complete List of Seminar Dates and Sites, 1979-1984 (Reel 125, Frame 109)
        - Congressional Seminars, 1985-1992 (Reel 125, Frame 130)
          See Box 1, Folder 7, for photographs.
        - Congressional Workshop, 1991 (Reel 125, Frame 227)
        - Criminal Justice Programs, November 18, 1982 (Reel 125, Frame 288)
        - Donors Forum of Chicago, 1988-1989 (Reel 125, Frame 302)
        - Equitable Seminars, 1981-1985 (Reel 125, Frame 336)
        - Equitable Seminars - Planning Notes, 1981-1982 (Reel 125, Frame 470)
        - Equitable Seminars - Summary Sheets, 1982-1985 (Reel 125, Frame 537)
        - The Foundation Center Accession List, January 1976-December 1977 (Reel 125, Frame 646)
        - The Foundation Center Pamphlets, 1973-1978 (Reel 125, Frame 730)
        - Foundation Funding in New York State, September 28, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 760)
        - Fund Fare Exchange, 1990-1991 (Reel 125, Frame 797)
        - Grant Seeking in Mississippi, November 6-7, 1986 (Reel 125, Frame 820)
        - Deborah Koch - Congressional Sunbelt Caucus, 1992 (Reel 125, Frame 850)
        - Kresge Foundation Program, 1992-1993 (Reel 125, Frame 862)
        - Levi Strauss Foundation - Proposals, Seminars, Correspondence, 1980-1986 (Reel 125, Frame 886)
        - McDonald's Report, 1979-1981 (Reel 125, Frame 982)
        - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - A Grantmaker's Introduction to the Foundation Center, May 1, 1987 (Reel 125, Frame 1105)
        - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - A Grantmaker's Introduction to the Foundation Center, March 8, 1989, May 11, 1989 (Reel 125, Frame 1154)
        - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers - A Grantmaker's Introduction to the Foundation Center, February 21, 1990 (Reel 125, Frame 1171)
        - New York State Charities Law - Panel, 1986-1987 (Reel 125, Frame 1178)
        - Peat Marwick Seminars, 1988-1989 (Reel 126, Frame 1)
        - Regional Seminars for Grant Seekers, 1984-1985 (Reel 126, Frame 112)
        - Resource Development Systems Seminar, 1988 (Reel 126, Frame 120)
        - Michael S. Seltzer, 1981-1982 (Reel 126, Frame 139)
        - Seminar for the Aged, 1982 (Reel 126, Frame 169)
        - Seminar Ideas, 1984-1987 (Reel 126, Frame 189)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 193)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Board Development, April 9, 1981, June 111, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 310)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Budget Preparation and Fiscal Planning, March 26, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 347)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Corporate Funding, March 19, 1981, May 21, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 422)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Direct Mail and Special Events, April 16, 1981, June 18, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 473)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Effective Public Relations for Non-Profits, June 25, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 574)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Foundation Funding, March 12, 1981, May 7, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 622)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Government Funding, April 2, 1981, June 4, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 660)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Legal Problems, April 23, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 720)
        - Technical Assistance Seminars - Program Planning and Proposal Writing, March 5, 1981 (Reel 126, Frame 755)
      - Program and Project Files - Programs - Programs - Source Book Profiles, 1977-1994; 8
        Source Book Profiles was a loose leaf based book that contained important and public information on the top one thousand foundations in the United States compiled by The Foundation Center.
        - Analysis, 1990 (Reel 126, Frame 806)
        - Changes, 1990-1991 (Reel 126, Frame 827)
        - Corporate Mailing Responses, 1978 (Reel 126, Frame 954)
        - Correspondence, 1979 (Reel 126, Frame 975)
        - Cost Reduction Measures for Series 3, 1979 (Reel 126, Frame 1120)
        - Foundation 1000 - Revamp, 1994 (Reel 126, Frame 1130)
        - Foundation Staff Survey, 1982 (Reel 126, Frame 1243)
        - Historical - Series 2 and 3, 1979-1980 (Reel 127, Frame 1)
        - Index Redesign, 1984-1985 (Reel 127, Frame 178)
        - Index Redesign, 1989-1990 (Reel 127, Frame 232)
        - Indexing Procedures, 1977-1978 (Reel 127, Frame 395)
        - Initial Materials Consulted for Source Books Profiles, 1977 (Reel 127, Frame 467)
        - Initial Printing and Mailing Estimates, 1977 (Reel 127, Frame 521)
        - Initial Reactions to Proposed Format, 1977 (Reel 127, Frame 529)
        - Issues and Grant Numbers, 1989 (Reel 127, Frame 549)
        - Mailing List, 1977-1979 (Reel 127, Frame 585)
        - Mailing List Removal Due to Non-Payment, 1978-1979 (Reel 127, Frame 654)
        - Narrative Shell, 1989-1990 (Reel 127, Frame 665)
        - Original Guide to Foundation Profile Updates, 1978 (Reel 127, Frame 788)
        - Original Guidelines, undated (Reel 127, Frame 798)
        - Purchasers of Series 1, 1979 (Reel 127, Frame 850)
        - Questionnaire, 1978 (Reel 127, Frame 922)
        - Reference Manual, 1980-1982 (Reel 127, Frame 964)
        - Renewal Information for Series 3, 1979-1980 (Reel 127, Frame 1084)
        - Response Rates, 1978 (Reel 127, Frame 1141)
        - Revamp, 1981-1985 (Reel 128, Frame 1)
        - Source Profile 13, 1988-1989 (Reel 128, Frame 43)
        - Source Profile 13, 1990 (Reel 128, Frame 140)
        - Statistical Tables, 1989-1990 (Reel 128, Frame 349)
        - Taft Organization, 1979 (Reel 128, Frame 588)
    - Prospects, 1972-1991; E
      This series contains material on foundations who were not annual contributors to The Foundation Center, and the solicitation of donations from these foundations on behalf of The Foundation Center.
      - Declined Fund-Raising Letters (A-C), 1985-1990 (Reel 128, Frame 598)
      - Declined Fund-Raising Letters (D-H), 1985-1991 (Reel 128, Frame 758)
      - Declined Fund-Raising Letters (I-M), 1985-1987 (Reel 128, Frame 938)
      - Declined Fund-Raising Letters (N-S), 1985-1989 (Reel 128, Frame 1073)
      - Declined Fund-Raising Letters (T-Y), 1985-1986 (Reel 128, Frame 1228)
      - Fund-Raising Letters, 1972-1979 (Reel 129, Frame 1)
      - Fund-Raising Letters, 1975-1979 (Reel 129, Frame 65)
      - Mailing Results of Prospects, 1989-1990 (Reel 129, Frame 168)
      - Prospect Strategies of the 1970's, 1976-1979 (Reel 129, Frame 178)
      - Prospects, 1978 (Reel 129, Frame 210)
      - Prospects, 1981 (Reel 129, Frame 214)
      - Prospects, 1983-1985 (Reel 129, Frame 241)
      - Prospects, 1985-1986 (Reel 129, Frame 379)
      - AAV Foundation - Marshall H. and Nellie Alworth Memorial Fund, 1972-1979 (Reel 129, Frame 423)
      - Maurice Amado Foundation - The ARW Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 129, Frame 702)
      - ASARCO Foundation - The R. C. Baker Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 129, Frame 1024)
      - Summerfield Baldwin, Jr. Foundation - S. D. Bechtel, Jr. Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 130, Frame 1)
      - The Bedford Fund, Inc. - Bezalel Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 130, Frame 242)
      - The Bibb Foundation, Inc. - Borg-Warner Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 130, Frame 501)
      - Boston Fatherless and Widows Society - Carrie Baum Browning Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 130, Frame 820)
      - Broyhill Foundation, Inc. - Milton H. Callner Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 131, Frame 1)
      - The Cambridge Foundation - Carter Fund, 1972-1979 (Reel 131, Frame 242)
      - Casey Family Program - Chichester du Pont Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 131, Frame 493)
      - Children's Foundation of Erie County, Inc. - Cluett, Peabody and Company Inc., 1972-1981 (Reel 131, Frame 765)
      - Ty Cobb Educational Foundation - Cooper Industries Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 131, Frame 961)
      - Copeland Andelot Foundation, Inc. - Crystal Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 132, Frame 1)
      - The Patrick and Anna M. Cudahy Fund - The Westmoreland Davis Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 132, Frame 277)
      - Davison-Foreman Foundation - The Deutsch Foundation, 1974-1981 (Reel 132, Frame 498)
      - De Vilbiss Fund - Doyle Charitable Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 132, Frame 716)
      - Dravo Corporation and Subsidiaries Charitable Trust - Jack Eckerd Corporation Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 132, Frame 975)
      - C. K. Eddy Family Memorial Fund - The J. F. Ervin Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 133, Frame 1)
      - ESB Foundation - S. C. Feuerstein Family Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 133, Frame 254)
      - Fidelity Foundation - Albert W. and Edith V. Flowers Charitable Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 133, Frame 495)
      - FMC Foundation - Herman Frasch Foundation for Chemical Research, 1972-1979 (Reel 133, Frame 741)
      - Free Quaker Society - Gazette Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 133, Frame 983)
      - The Carl Gellert Foundation - Girard Trust Bank Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 134, Frame 1)
      - Lenora and Alfred Glancy Foundation, Inc. - Josephine H. Graeber Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 134, Frame 180)
      - The Greater Kanawha Valley Foundation - G. A. C. Halff Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 134, Frame 450)
      - Hall Foundation Fund - Merrill G. and Emita E. Hastings Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 134, Frame 722)
      - Margaret Milliken Hatch Charitable Trust - Hervey Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 134, Frame 940)
      - Hess Foundation, Inc. - James and Lynelle Holden Fund, 1974-1979 (Reel 134, Frame 1202)
      - The Hollywood Canteen Foundation - The Humphreys Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 135, Frame 1)
      - The Hunt Foundation - Joe Ingram Trust, 1972-1980 (Reel 135, Frame 220)
      - Initial Teaching Alphabet Foundation - Leon Jaworski Foundation, 1972-1981 (Reel 135, Frame 472)
      - Michael Jeffers Memorial Foundation - Edith C. Justus Trust and Samuel Justus Charitable Trust, 1972-1981 (Reel 135, Frame 735)
      - Kachelmacher Memorial, Inc. - Harris and Eliza Kemper Fund, 1972-1981 (Reel 136, Frame 1)
      - The George R. Kendall Foundation - The Kirkpatrick Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 136, Frame 205)
      - The David and Sadie Klau Foundation - Lanier Brothers Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 136, Frame 418)
      - Mary P. Lard Trust - Margaret and Irvin Lesher Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 136, Frame 737)
      - The Letourneau Foundation - Linn-Henley Charitable Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 136, Frame 945)
      - Lippman Schnurmacher Fund, Inc. - Bertha Russ Lytel Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 137, Frame 1)
      - The M. E. Foundation - Maryland National Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 137, Frame 262)
      - Massachusetts Society of Cincinnati - Charles L. McCune Charitable Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 137, Frame 547)
      - The McDermott Foundation - McWilliams Memorial Hospital Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 137, Frame 831)
      - Mead Corporation Foundation - Allen H. Meyers Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 137, Frame 1115)
      - Herbert I. and Elsa B. Michael Foundation - The John Motley Morehead Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 138, Frame 1)
      - The Morgan City Fund - Myra Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 138, Frame 220)
      - N. F. L. Alumni Foundation Fund - Carl A. Norgren Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 138, Frame 413)
      - The Norman Foundation, Inc. - Lottie E. Olberg Testamentary Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 138, Frame 725)
      - Old Stone Bank Educational Foundation - The Frank Loomis Palmer Fund, 1974-1979 (Reel 138, Frame 959)
      - Pamplin Foundation - The M. G. and Johnnye D. Perry Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 138, Frame 1155)
      - The Pet Milk Foundation - The Pilgrim Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 1)
      - Pine Level Foundation, Inc. - Pritzker Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 247)
      - Prospect Hill Foundation - Ransom Fidelity Company, 1972-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 479)
      - The Rapids-Standard Foundation - Donald A. Rhoades Family Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 679)
      - Eugene J. and Corinne A. Ribakoff Charitable Foundation - Fred M. Roddy Charitable Trust, 1974-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 908)
      - Rogers Brothers Foundation Inc. - Edward Rutledge Charity, 1972-1979 (Reel 139, Frame 1117)
      - The S & H Foundation, Inc. - S. H. and Helen R. Scheuer Family Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 140, Frame 1)
      - The Schiff Foundation - George and Effie Seay Memorial Trust, 1972-1979 (Reel 140, Frame 226)
      - Charles See Foundation - The Thomas B. and Elizabeth M. Sheridan Foundation, Inc., 1974-1981 (Reel 140, Frame 472)
      - Sherman Foundation - The Stanley Smith Horticultural Trust, 1974-1980 (Reel 140, Frame 678)
      - Frank L. and Laura L. Smock Foundation - Stackpole-Hall Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 140, Frame 883)
      - A. E. Staley Manufacturing Company - The Steel-Reese Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 140, Frame 1145)
      - Jules and Doris Stein Foundation - Stop and Shop Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 141, Frame 1)
      - The Louis L. Stott Foundation - Doss T. Sutton Charitable Foundation, 1974-1982 (Reel 141, Frame 241)
      - The Swanson Foundation - Edgar A. Thurman Charitable Foundation for Children, 1972-1981 (Reel 141, Frame 468)
      - Ticor Foundation - Tyler Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 141, Frame 758)
      - UMC Industries Foundation, Inc. - UVB Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 141, Frame 1010)
      - The Vale-Asche Foundation - Wahlert Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 1)
      - The Walgreen Benefit Fund - Rama Watumull Fund, 1972-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 202)
      - The Raymond John Wean Foundation - The Frederick and Margaret Weyerhaeuser Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 439)
      - Wheeler Foundation - J. Harvie Wilkinson, Jr. Charitable Foundation Trust, 1974-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 687)
      - Gordon Fay Willey Trust - Woman's Seamen's Friend Society of Connecticut, 1974-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 887)
      - Cornelius A. and Muriel P. Wood Charity Fund - Marie and John Zimmermann Fund, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 142, Frame 1144)
    - Sponsors, 1972-1985; F
      This series contains material on foundations that made annual donations to The Foundation Center. At the beginning of this series, there is a grouping of attachments that have been filmed labeled Attachments. They were duplicated throughout the series, and the duplicates have been removed to save space and repetition.
      - Sponsor Summary Sheets, 1985 (Reel 143, Frame 2)
      - Support Granted or Pledged for 1976-1977 (Reel 143, Frame 30)